Contact

gcoletti@llu.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/giuliana-coletti-a56a24105 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Professional Working) English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

PFCCS

CRRT -Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy CCRN

Honors-Awards

Daisy Award Nominee
Unit award of Excellence

Giuliana Coletti

BSN, RN, CCRN

Redlands, California

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Inpatient Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nurse from Loma Linda University.

Experience

Loma Linda University Childrens Hospital Registered Nurse August 2014 - Present (5 years 11 months) Loma Linda, CA

August/2014 to present - Loma Linda University Children's Hospital PICU. The pediatric intensive care unit (PICU) at LLUCH is a 25-bed state-of-the-art facility serving the entire four-county Inland Empire containing a population of over four million. This bustling unit averages 110 admissions per month which provides residents with exposure to a vast variety of critical care patients. Approximately one-half of the admissions are brought in by transport services, including ground vehicles, helicopters, and fixed-winged aircrafts.

Education

Loma Linda University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2014)